<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Xiangyi&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://xiangyi.pro/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Xiangyi&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 10:29:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://xiangyi.pro/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OSI 7-Layer Model</title>
      <link>http://xiangyi.pro/2020/osi-7-layer-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 10:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiangyi.pro/2020/osi-7-layer-model/</guid>
      <description>The Open System Interconnection (OSI) model (defined in ISO 7498-1), which is a reference tool for understanding data communications between two networked systems, divides the communication processes into 7 layers:
 Physical layer Data link layer Network layer Transport layer Session layer Presentation layer Application layer  Those layers break up the networks into manageable pioeces, which provides a common language to explain components and their functionalities. Here this article will give an overview of the 7 layers top-to-down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Config oh-my-posh on Windows 10</title>
      <link>http://xiangyi.pro/2020/oh-my-posh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 07:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiangyi.pro/2020/oh-my-posh/</guid>
      <description>oh-my-posh, as an alternative of oh-my-zsh in *nix-based system, is a beautiful theme engine for Powershell in Windows Terminal.
Prerequisites  Windows Terminal Git Powerline fonts (at least one font is needed to be installed)  Installation Using the following commands to install the oh-my-posh in your Windows Terminal:
Install-Module posh-git -Scope CurrentUser Install-Module oh-my-posh -Scope CurrentUser Now the oh-my-posh is successfully installed on your computer, the following commands are used to enable the prompt:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>